Walter Dorwin Teague Papers
Walter Dorwin Teague Papers
- Oversize material
  - Drawings, sketches, illustrations, Canadian Oil Refineries Ltd., CANO, Marion County Courthouse, Eleutharian Mills, USA, Banco de Ponce, Hagely Museum, "Facing System," Barcalo Manufacturing (Oversize 25)
  - Miscellaneous, Eleutharian Mills Museum, "Industry on the Brandywine" glass plate negatives (2), illustrations for reproduction (mounted, color) (Oversize 26)